http://www.ecardz.co.nz/privacy-and-disclaimer/

Privacy and Disclaimer - ID cards, ID card printing and loyalty cards by Ecardz - Ask about our solutions for ID cards, ID card printing, identification cards, and Loyalty cards
Have Any Questions?Phone: (03) 359 0026
Stay Connected:
HomeID CardsID Card AccessoriesCard PrintersPointman ID PrintersID Printer Pointman TP9200ID Printer Pointman NuviaID Printer ConsumablesFargo ID PrintersFargo Printer – C50Fargo Printer – DTC1250eFargo Printer – DTC4250ePlastic CardsPlastic Card PrintingMembership CardsColoured CardsPlain CardsSmart CardsBarcodeMagnetic Stripe CardsID Card AccessoriesEco-Friendly cardsAdding Card Holder DetailsNFC TagsSolutionsQuidzCandoAbout UsBlogContact UsHomeID CardsID Card AccessoriesCard PrintersPointman ID PrintersID Printer Pointman TP9200ID Printer Pointman NuviaID Printer ConsumablesFargo ID PrintersFargo Printer – C50Fargo Printer – DTC1250eFargo Printer – DTC4250ePlastic CardsPlastic Card PrintingMembership CardsColoured CardsPlain CardsSmart CardsBarcodeMagnetic Stripe CardsID Card AccessoriesEco-Friendly cardsAdding Card Holder DetailsNFC TagsSolutionsQuidzCandoAbout UsBlogContact Us
Get a QuotePrivacy and DisclaimerThis Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Ecardz collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the http://www.ecardz.co.nz website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Ecardz.Personal identification informationWe may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.Non-personal identification informationWe may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.Web browser cookiesOur Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.How we use collected informationEcardz may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:– To improve customer serviceInformation you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.– To improve our SiteWe may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.– To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site featureTo send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.– To send periodic emailsWe may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.How we protect your informationWe adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.Sharing your personal informationWe do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.Changes to this privacy policyEcardz has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and send you an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.Your acceptance of these termsBy using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.Contacting usIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please feel free to contact us.This document was last updated on February 14, 2013
Ecardz has successfully serviced the NZ market since 1998 with ID card printers and consumables as well as plain and printed plastic cards and radio frequency tags & tokens.
Read More
Sales Terms and Conditions
Privacy Policy
Terms of Use
Read MoreContact UsAddress: Auckland Office: Level 27, PwC building, 188 Quay St, Auckland.
Canterbury Office: D/210 High Street, Waimakariri, Rangiora 7400 Phone: +64 (03) 359 0026Email: chris@authenticate.co.nz
Ecardz Ltd has an overal satisfaction rating of
4.8 out of 5 based on 7 paying customer review and rating.
